<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <gameList>
   <game>
     <path>./anguna.bin</path>
     <name>Anguna 2600</name>
     <desc>This time, you are on a quest to defeat the Goblin King. Like last time, you got captured early on, and must battle your way through 5 dungeons before confronting him!</desc>
     <image>./anguna.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20160524T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Nathan Tolbert</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Anguna 2600</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./bitquest.bin</path>
     <name>Bit Quest</name>
     <desc>In Bit Quest, you take the role of a 'bit knight' who must rescue the princess of the bits. She is locked away in an evil castle guarded by dragons (of course!) Explore the world and uncover the locations of dungeons, and save the princess! To aid you in your quest, there is an ancient sword that can be used to attack monsters! (Once you find the sword, use the joystick button to attack!)</desc>
     <image>./bitquest.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170811T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Bit Quest</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./bitquest2.bin</path>
     <name>Bit Quest II</name>
     <desc>Bit Quest II continues the story of Bit Quest. After rescuing the princess, the warrior is captured by the ruthless Baron Von Darkbit! Bit Quest II features an even larger world to explore with many hidden dungeons scattered throughout the many lands. Gameplay is simple! Use the joystick to move the princess, and press the fire button to attack with the sword. Pressing the GAME SELECT switch will display a map and show an inventory of the keys you have found. Pressing the switch again, or hitting the fire button will resume the game. The GAME RESET switch can be used to start the game over at the bit's castle. The left difficulty switch controls how strong some monsters are. On the title screen, press either the fire button or the reset switch to begin a new game. OBJECTIVE: Explore the world, and find the 4 hidden keys to unlock the Baron's castle and rescue the bit warrior! Watch out for monsters and their attacks.</desc>
     <image>./bitquest2.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20190116T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Bit Quest II v.14</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./dkarcade2600.bin</path>
     <name>DK Arcade 2600</name>
     <desc>Save Lady Pauline! Points are awarded for jumping over obstacles, destroying objects with the hammer, completing levels and collecting various items. This playable demo features all four levels but will end after the rivet level (Level 4).</desc>
     <image>./dkarcade2600.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20141016T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Byte Knight</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>DK Arcade 2600 (playable demo)</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./emr.bin</path>
     <name>Evil Magician Returns</name>
     <desc>Adventure-type game. The premise is that his dragons are now dead, so he and his apprentice have returned and captured the golden chalice. The Evil Magician (red wizard) has the ability to shoot fireballs, his apprentice (white wizard) does not.  You too have the ability to shoot fireballs after you've acquired the staff. The red wizard tends to guard certain items,  while the white wizard avoids them.  You've also brought a backpack with you this time so you can carry multiple items. The game has no sound...</desc>
     <image>./emr.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20090607T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Byte Knight</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Evil Magician Returns</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./emrii.bin</path>
     <name>Evil Magician Returns II</name>
     <desc>In Evil Magician Returns II you must reclaim the chalice from the Evil Magician and his apprentice. There are now four castles to explore, complete with mazes and secret passageways. Home castle gate is now open - why should you have to open your own castle? You can only carry one item like Adventure. The staff also acts as a magnet to attract objects by holding down the button. A new hideous Dragon created by the Evil Magician guards the chalice on Levels 2 and 3. And many more...</desc>
     <image>./emrii.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20161126T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Byte Knight</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Evil Magician Returns II</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./fishy.bin</path>
     <name>Fishy</name>
     <desc>For one or two players - whichever fish collects 5 points first, wins. Grab the power-ups to transform!</desc>
     <image>./fishy.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Fishy v.2</genre>
     <players>1-2</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./flappy_the_duck.bin</path>
     <name>Flappy the Duck</name>
     <desc>Tap to flap! Use the joystick button to flap, but don't hit the walls. Grab hearts for extra points. This game features two difficulty levels (via left switch.)</desc>
     <image>./flappy_the_duck.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20181231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Flappy the Duck</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./halo2600.bin</path>
     <name>Halo 2600</name>
     <desc>At first you have the player battling through a series of rooms. You had to kill all the enemies before it would unlock the walls and let you move to the next room. After defeating the boss, you will enter the legendary mode, so that if you beat the game you can play all the way through it again with a few parameters tweaked to make it much tougher.</desc>
     <image>./halo2600.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20100801T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Ed Fries</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Halo 2600</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./hauntedbakery.bin</path>
     <name>Haunted Bakery</name>
     <desc>You play as a giraffe and crocodile named  Emelie and Maxwell, respectively. They have somehow found themselves in a haunted bakery and decided to try to photograph some ghosts! You can switch between the two characters by flipping the Select switch. WARNING: This game makes use of flickering graphics. Please be careful if you are sensitive to that sort of thing.</desc>
     <image>./hauntedbakery.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180128T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Denebola Interactive (Phano)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Emelie and Maxwell in The Case of the Haunted Bakery [v.1.0]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./jammed.bin</path>
     <name>Jammed</name>
     <desc>Move all the other cars out of the way to steal your dream car out of the lot. Jammed consists of 600 puzzles which are organized in 6 difficulty levels of 100 puzzles each. With the joystick you can move the cursor and the firebutton moves the selected car in the indicated direction. JAMMED is based on the board game Rush Hour from Binary Arts.</desc>
     <image>./jammed.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20021216T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Thomas Jentzsch</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Jammed</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./kellykangaroo.bin</path>
     <name>Kelly Kangaroo</name>
     <desc>Kelly the kangaroo is enjoying a lovely picnic date with Rosie the rabbit in the picturesque Mossy Valley when - Oh no!  The mad scientist Contemptus Mundy, always bitter and jealous of the happy people living on Gaia Gaia Island, has kidnapped Rosie and locked her away in his motherbase in the clouds! It's up to you to help Kelly save her sweetheart before it's too late and that vile Contemptus whisks her away to the stars.</desc>
     <image>./kellykangaroo.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180309T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Denebola Interactive (Phano)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Kelly Kangaroo [v.0.6]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./nanowing.bin</path>
     <name>NanoWing 2600</name>
     <desc>A prequel to the 2005 metalbabble.com game "NanoWing" - avoid the obstacles while hurdling through hyperspace!</desc>
     <image>./nanowing.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>NanoWing 2600</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./neko_2600.bin</path>
     <name>Neko 2600</name>
     <desc>A small experiment/game with gravity and simple ball physics. Hold left or right to pick a direction, then press the fire button to launch a ball.Aim for the moving targets below to rack up the points. Use the "Game Select" switch to select levels.</desc>
     <image>./neko_2600.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20181231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Neko 2600</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./pothole.bin</path>
     <name>PotHole</name>
     <desc>Dodge the potholes, and collect the power ups!</desc>
     <image>./pothole.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>PotHole</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./roboninjaclimb.bin</path>
     <name>Robo-Ninja Climb</name>
     <desc>Robo-Ninja is at it again, this time practicing his climbing and jumping skills before setting out to save the world. In this NES game, you climb and dodge spikes, navigating 5 levels of obstacles.</desc>
     <image>./roboninjaclimb.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171122T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Nathan Tolbert</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Robo-Ninja Climb</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./runtysrevenge.bin</path>
     <name>Runty's Revenge</name>
     <desc>It is a rom made about my dog Runty and my Wife chasing him around.</desc>
     <image>./runtysrevenge.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20181015T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Guillermo Gee (Squidsee)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Runty's Revenge</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./sandcastles.bin</path>
     <name>Sand Castles</name>
     <desc>Jump and shoot the enemies to clear each level - but don't take too long or you'll get chased by the "reaper". Left difficulty switch controls game difficulty, right switch turns music on/off. This game is also compatible with SEGA Genesis controllers!</desc>
     <image>./sandcastles.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171126T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Sand Castles</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./solarplexus.bin</path>
     <name>Solar Plexus</name>
     <desc>What starts out as a routine hunt for salvage in the far reaches of the galaxy turns into a white-knuckle fight for survival in Solar Plexus, the first Atari 2600 release by independent game developer JessCREATIONS*, Co. It'll take sharp reflexes to keep your starskimmer full of fuel and away from the wildly unpredictable artificial sun which threatens to make every move your last! The Solar Plexus increases in speed and mutates into new, more dangerous forms as you continue to play. If one fiery orb bouncing around the screen was hard enough for you to handle, just wait until you have to deal with two, or even three of them! Only the best players will last long enough to witness the final form of this relentless foe.</desc>
     <image>./solarplexus.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20051231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Jess Ragan</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Solar Plexus</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./stardust.bin</path>
     <name>Stardust</name>
     <desc>Explore the galaxy, zap aliens, blast asteroids, uncover the locations of distant planets, and defeat the evil forces of the mysterious Dark Queen.</desc>
     <image>./stardust.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180115T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Brian W. Shea (Metalbabble)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Stardust</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./threes.bin</path>
     <name>Three.s</name>
     <desc>A port of the 2048 game to the Atari 2600. Original name: 2^11 (2048). You get points for merging tiles, scores tripple for each higher number. The game ends when no tile can be moved.</desc>
     <image>./threes.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20140810T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Thomas Jentzsch</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Three.s [v.1.02]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./thrust.bin</path>
     <name>Thrust</name>
     <desc>The resistance is about to launch a major offensive against the Intergalactic Empire. In preparation for this, they have captured several battle-grade starships, but they lack the essential power sources for these formidable craft; Klystron Pods. You have been commissioned by the resistance to steal these pods from the Empire's storage planets. Each planet is defended by a battery of "Limpet" guns, powered by a nuclear power plant. By firing shots at the power plant, the guns can be temporarily disabled; the more shots fired at the nuclear reactor, the longer the guns will take to recharge. BUT BEWARE!! If you fire too many shots at the reactor, it will become critical, giving you just ten seconds to clear the planet before it is destroyed. If you have not already retrieved the pod stored at that planet, then you will have failed the mission. If you have retrieved the pod, and you manage to send the reactor into its critical phase, and leave the planet safely, you will receive a hefty bonus. Further into the Empire's system, you will encounter planets with REVERSE GRAVITY and something even more deadly...</desc>
     <image>./thrust.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20040609T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Thomas Jentzsch</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Thrust [v.1.27]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./turtlebay.bin</path>
     <name>Turtle Bay</name>
     <desc>Turtle Bay is a very simple Atari 2600 game.  You are a turtle which needs to eat food and escape a bird to advance closer to the ocean. As you can expect it is a very simple arcade game.</desc>
     <image>./turtlebay.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180827T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Unlink2</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Turtle Bay</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./winterfortress.bin</path>
     <name>Winter Fortress</name>
     <desc>Six pesky little penguin chicks have run off and gotten lost in the mysterious ruins. You are the only one brave enough to rescue them! Roll snowballs by holding down the fire button and letting go to smash them against the iceblocks. Only larger snowballs will break the blocks. But don't get too close; this ice is so cold, you will be frozen solid if you touch it! If this wasn't bad enough, all this activity has awakened the old sentinals. Avoid their eerie mechanical movements by throwing snowballs at them. But be quick about it because they will start rebuilding their fortress with new blocks! If you can save six chicks without getting frozen, you are rewarded with an extra penguin</desc>
     <image>./winterfortress.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180128T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Denebola Interactive (Phano)</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Winter Fortress [v.0.5]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
 </gameList>